[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "You bowed to Lady Gaga?", "question_tokens": ["You", "bowed", "to", "Lady", "Gaga", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "I bowed to Lady Gaga.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "bowed", "to", "Lady", "Gaga", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack"]}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "What did he say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "Hi, I'm Barack.", "answer_tokens": ["Hi", ",", "I", "'m", "Barack", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Mr. President"]}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "What do you call the president?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "call", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "Oh, when I see him I call him Barack or President Obama or Mr. President.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "when", "I", "see", "him", "I", "call", "him", "Barack", "or", "President", "Obama", "or", "Mr.", "President", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "How do you do?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "I'm great, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "great", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "How old are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "I am turning 21 in two weeks.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "turning", "21", "in", "two", "weeks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "How did you do this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "I have a fantastic publicity team.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "fantastic", "publicity", "team", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 79, "question": "I mean, you weren't even -- you weren't doing anything before you got this job, were you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "were", "n't", "even", "--", "you", "were", "n't", "doing", "anything", "before", "you", "got", "this", "job", ",", "were", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "No, no, I was just a student and I was in high school a few months before I got the show, and then I was in college for two weeks, and then when I officially got it and -- I was working at a dry cleaner's in the summers to --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "I", "was", "just", "a", "student", "and", "I", "was", "in", "high", "school", "a", "few", "months", "before", "I", "got", "the", "show", ",", "and", "then", "I", "was", "in", "college", "for", "two", "weeks", ",", "and", "then", "when", "I", "officially", "got", "it", "and", "--", "I", "was", "working", "at", "a", "dry", "cleaner", "'s", "in", "the", "summers", "to", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Earning how much?", "question_tokens": ["Earning", "how", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "I think it was -- oh, gosh!", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "was", "--", "oh", ",", "gosh", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "-- about \"Glee\"?", "question_tokens": ["--", "about", "``", "Glee", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "``", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Well, I was driving back from the last audition, and I was -- my mom, my mom was driving.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "driving", "back", "from", "the", "last", "audition", ",", "and", "I", "was", "--", "my", "mom", ",", "my", "mom", "was", "driving", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", ":", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "What's the look?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "look", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "The look was -- like, it looked like she should be driving, she should be paying attention to the road.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "look", "was", "--", "like", ",", "it", "looked", "like", "she", "should", "be", "driving", ",", "she", "should", "be", "paying", "attention", "to", "the", "road", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Did you have an inkling?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "an", "inkling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "I mean, who could've predicted all of this?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "who", "could", "'ve", "predicted", "all", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "I literally cannot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "literally", "can", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Were you thinking in your head, \"I really want to be\" -- I don't know, whoever?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "thinking", "in", "your", "head", ",", "``", "I", "really", "want", "to", "be", "''", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "whoever", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "``", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "''", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "I think I --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Tom Cruise, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Tom", "Cruise", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Zac Efron?", "question_tokens": ["Zac", "Efron", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Definitely -- definitely not, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Definitely", "--", "definitely", "not", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zac Efron"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Who are your idols?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "your", "idols", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "No, I never thought I would ever be of heartthrob stature.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "never", "thought", "I", "would", "ever", "be", "of", "heartthrob", "stature", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Who were your celebrity icons?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "were", "your", "celebrity", "icons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Oh, gosh!", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "gosh", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Well, not actually Oprah?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "not", "actually", "Oprah", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "CC", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Did you want to be an actor?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "want", "to", "be", "an", "actor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Yes, ever since -- I remember I was, like, 3 years old, and I was watching a movie, the title of which escapes me, but -- and I remember the credits came on.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "ever", "since", "--", "I", "remember", "I", "was", ",", "like", ",", "3", "years", "old", ",", "and", "I", "was", "watching", "a", "movie", ",", "the", "title", "of", "which", "escapes", "me", ",", "but", "--", "and", "I", "remember", "the", "credits", "came", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "When did it pop for you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "it", "pop", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Oh, God -- what was the first \"pinch me\" moment?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "God", "--", "what", "was", "the", "first", "``", "pinch", "me", "''", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "``", "NN", "PRP", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "The moment when you rang your mum and you were both getting carried away on the phone.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "moment", "when", "you", "rang", "your", "mum", "and", "you", "were", "both", "getting", "carried", "away", "on", "the", "phone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 200, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "When I signed up for \"America's Got Talent.\"", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "signed", "up", "for", "``", "America", "'s", "Got", "Talent", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "I mean, the first day of filming the live shows was through those famous gates.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "the", "first", "day", "of", "filming", "the", "live", "shows", "was", "through", "those", "famous", "gates", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Now, that is a moment, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "that", "is", "a", "moment", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Yes, it's an amazing feeling, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "an", "amazing", "feeling", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "It's just kids who feel they're outsiders, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "kids", "who", "feel", "they", "'re", "outsiders", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Right, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "EX", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "But as you were walking up, you just thought -- what were you thinking?", "question_tokens": ["But", "as", "you", "were", "walking", "up", ",", "you", "just", "thought", "--", "what", "were", "you", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "I remember when I was walking up, I kept thinking to myself: do not trip on a chair or a table on the way up there, because it was so possible, because there were so many things in my way.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "remember", "when", "I", "was", "walking", "up", ",", "I", "kept", "thinking", "to", "myself", ":", "do", "not", "trip", "on", "a", "chair", "or", "a", "table", "on", "the", "way", "up", "there", ",", "because", "it", "was", "so", "possible", ",", "because", "there", "were", "so", "many", "things", "in", "my", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Do you remember their names?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "remember", "their", "names", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Is there anyone in particular that you'd like to just smoke out now?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anyone", "in", "particular", "that", "you", "'d", "like", "to", "just", "smoke", "out", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "No, I hated them all equally, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "hated", "them", "all", "equally", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "How did it make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "it", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "I was just embarrassed, because -- I mean, I would walk by these people that I barely knew in the hallway, and they'd just scream profanities at me that I didn't think were true at the time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "just", "embarrassed", ",", "because", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "would", "walk", "by", "these", "people", "that", "I", "barely", "knew", "in", "the", "hallway", ",", "and", "they", "'d", "just", "scream", "profanities", "at", "me", "that", "I", "did", "n't", "think", "were", "true", "at", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "To me, she's just a phenomenon who completely gets what it takes to be a modern-day brand, doesn't she?", "question_tokens": ["To", "me", ",", "she", "'s", "just", "a", "phenomenon", "who", "completely", "gets", "what", "it", "takes", "to", "be", "a", "modern-day", "brand", ",", "does", "n't", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Did you meet her when she came on?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "meet", "her", "when", "she", "came", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "A couple times.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "couple", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "What did you make of her?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Well, I completely embarrassed myself to no end.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "completely", "embarrassed", "myself", "to", "no", "end", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "You bowed to Lady Gaga?", "question_tokens": ["You", "bowed", "to", "Lady", "Gaga", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "I bowed to Lady Gaga.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "bowed", "to", "Lady", "Gaga", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "PRP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 322, "question": "What did she say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "she", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "\"Thank you.\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Thank", "you", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Did you have to, then, do anything else?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "to", ",", "then", ",", "do", "anything", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "No, I just ran.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "just", "ran", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Did you get to have a proper conversation with her?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "get", "to", "have", "a", "proper", "conversation", "with", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "No, I don't think I'll ever be able to have a proper conversation with her after that.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "'ll", "ever", "be", "able", "to", "have", "a", "proper", "conversation", "with", "her", "after", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", ":", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "You'd be too nervous?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'d", "be", "too", "nervous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "I'd be way too -- yes, right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "be", "way", "too", "--", "yes", ",", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Is she like an iconic figure for you?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "like", "an", "iconic", "figure", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "I -- you know, she's actually one of the first people in my generation whose music I liked.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "you", "know", ",", "she", "'s", "actually", "one", "of", "the", "first", "people", "in", "my", "generation", "whose", "music", "I", "liked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "NNS", "``", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 341, "question": "I bet they're just all over you like a rash about \"Glee,\" right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "bet", "they", "'re", "just", "all", "over", "you", "like", "a", "rash", "about", "``", "Glee", ",", "''", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Oh, everyone loves \"Glee.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "everyone", "loves", "``", "Glee", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Do you ever say to them, \"I know how you voted\"?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "say", "to", "them", ",", "``", "I", "know", "how", "you", "voted", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "''", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Well, here's the thing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "here", "'s", "the", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "But do you think that they will ever change their mind because you give them a picture?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "think", "that", "they", "will", "ever", "change", "their", "mind", "because", "you", "give", "them", "a", "picture", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Maybe.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "You know who they are when they ask you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "who", "they", "are", "when", "they", "ask", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "And you know how they voted?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "know", "how", "they", "voted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "I mean, do you feel like you're winning when you have that moment with them?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "like", "you", "'re", "winning", "when", "you", "have", "that", "moment", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "A little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Or do you feel that as gay rights become much more prominent and successes are being achieved, in a funny way, it's becoming in certain pockets, more homophobic as they try and resist this change?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "feel", "that", "as", "gay", "rights", "become", "much", "more", "prominent", "and", "successes", "are", "being", "achieved", ",", "in", "a", "funny", "way", ",", "it", "'s", "becoming", "in", "certain", "pockets", ",", "more", "homophobic", "as", "they", "try", "and", "resist", "this", "change", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "RBR", "JJ", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I don't know, because I know that I surround myself with positivity towards the situation and not negativity.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "because", "I", "know", "that", "I", "surround", "myself", "with", "positivity", "towards", "the", "situation", "and", "not", "negativity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "What kind of things?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "It was just -- high school again.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "just", "--", "high", "school", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "And that hurt?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "hurt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "Yes, because I mean, it's ridiculous when people have like strong opinions about you when it's about things you can't control.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "because", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "ridiculous", "when", "people", "have", "like", "strong", "opinions", "about", "you", "when", "it", "'s", "about", "things", "you", "ca", "n't", "control", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 408, "question": "It's all hand-in-hand, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "all", "hand-in-hand", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Right, it comes --", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "it", "comes", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "What did your mother say when she saw this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "your", "mother", "say", "when", "she", "saw", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "It's so funny.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "so", "funny", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "It's what mothers do, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "what", "mothers", "do", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "I mean, are you finding that you're getting more attractive because of the fame?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "are", "you", "finding", "that", "you", "'re", "getting", "more", "attractive", "because", "of", "the", "fame", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Oh, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "It's like fame is such a sort of magnet to people, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "like", "fame", "is", "such", "a", "sort", "of", "magnet", "to", "people", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Kind of, kind of.", "answer_tokens": ["Kind", "of", ",", "kind", "of", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "That goes with the territory, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "goes", "with", "the", "territory", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "That's -- yes, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "--", "yes", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Do you think you're -- are you equipped to deal with all this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "'re", "--", "are", "you", "equipped", "to", "deal", "with", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Sometimes.", "answer_tokens": ["Sometimes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "And what's behind-the-scenes stuff with you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "'s", "behind-the-scenes", "stuff", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "You know, like the security risks and the security issues that are very frightening that people don't know about, because I don't want them to know about.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "like", "the", "security", "risks", "and", "the", "security", "issues", "that", "are", "very", "frightening", "that", "people", "do", "n't", "know", "about", ",", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "them", "to", "know", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "What's the scariest thing that's happened to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "scariest", "thing", "that", "'s", "happened", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I was at a movie theater once, and I was by myself, stupidly, and I was semi-mobbed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "at", "a", "movie", "theater", "once", ",", "and", "I", "was", "by", "myself", ",", "stupidly", ",", "and", "I", "was", "semi-mobbed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "As it was going on, what were you thinking?", "question_tokens": ["As", "it", "was", "going", "on", ",", "what", "were", "you", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Not much.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "It was crazy, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "crazy", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "It's crazy, but I mean, in -- it's really a mind trip because, on one hand, you're -- you want them to stop.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "crazy", ",", "but", "I", "mean", ",", "in", "--", "it", "'s", "really", "a", "mind", "trip", "because", ",", "on", "one", "hand", ",", "you", "'re", "--", "you", "want", "them", "to", "stop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Have you had stalkers?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "had", "stalkers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Not -- not really.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "--", "not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Some form of stalking is flattering, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Some", "form", "of", "stalking", "is", "flattering", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "I mean, how can you trust people?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "how", "can", "you", "trust", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Life's a gamble, though, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Life", "'s", "a", "gamble", ",", "though", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Life is a gamble.", "answer_tokens": ["Life", "is", "a", "gamble", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", ":", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "How do you get your tears to work?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "get", "your", "tears", "to", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "It's really just a -- kind of like a glancing.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "really", "just", "a", "--", "kind", "of", "like", "a", "glancing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Can you do it now?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "do", "it", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Well, now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "How long would it take you to get into tear mode?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "would", "it", "take", "you", "to", "get", "into", "tear", "mode", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Well, it depends on the scene.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "depends", "on", "the", "scene", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "A minute?", "question_tokens": ["A", "minute", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "A minute.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "minute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ",", "PRP", "MD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "You could get tears in a couple of seconds?", "question_tokens": ["You", "could", "get", "tears", "in", "a", "couple", "of", "seconds", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "I could, I could, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "could", ",", "I", "could", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Well, not -- unless it's scripted.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "not", "--", "unless", "it", "'s", "scripted", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", ":"], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Is it like a magician revealing his secrets?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "like", "a", "magician", "revealing", "his", "secrets", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Yes, right, that's --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "right", ",", "that", "'s", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "You're feeling awkward about it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "feeling", "awkward", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "That's what it is.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "DT", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "To order?", "question_tokens": ["To", "order", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "No -- no, I mean it's -- no, because sometimes you just can't do it because your body can't produce tears, so you can't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "--", "no", ",", "I", "mean", "it", "'s", "--", "no", ",", "because", "sometimes", "you", "just", "ca", "n't", "do", "it", "because", "your", "body", "ca", "n't", "produce", "tears", ",", "so", "you", "ca", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "I don't think I've cried --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "'ve", "cried", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "When was the last time?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "last", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "The last time I cried.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "last", "time", "I", "cried", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "So, you're not actually that emotional off camera?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "you", "'re", "not", "actually", "that", "emotional", "off", "camera", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "WDT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "All that bullying, all that ostracizing?", "question_tokens": ["All", "that", "bullying", ",", "all", "that", "ostracizing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "VBG", ",", "DT", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "OLFER: Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["OLFER", ":", "Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "-- steelier side to you than you had when you were growing up?", "question_tokens": ["--", "steelier", "side", "to", "you", "than", "you", "had", "when", "you", "were", "growing", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "I think it made me a very sarcastic person, for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "made", "me", "a", "very", "sarcastic", "person", ",", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["4:00 in the morning"]}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "When did you finish working on this scene?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "finish", "working", "on", "this", "scene", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "We finished season two yesterday at 4:00 in the morning.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "finished", "season", "two", "yesterday", "at", "4:00", "in", "the", "morning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "And do you now get time off, or what happens?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "now", "get", "time", "off", ",", "or", "what", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", ",", "CC", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "And you're also doing a movie in all this?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "'re", "also", "doing", "a", "movie", "in", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["July 5th"], "LOCATION": ["LA"]}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "CD", "CC", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "How are you going to fit that in?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "going", "to", "fit", "that", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "Well, the tour ends on July 5th or 4th, I believe, and as soon as it's over, I am literally going straight to a plane and flying to the set in LA.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "tour", "ends", "on", "July", "5th", "or", "4th", ",", "I", "believe", ",", "and", "as", "soon", "as", "it", "'s", "over", ",", "I", "am", "literally", "going", "straight", "to", "a", "plane", "and", "flying", "to", "the", "set", "in", "LA", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "Do you get any time off at all?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "get", "any", "time", "off", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "Even a day?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "a", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Maybe -- I'll get like a day here and there.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "--", "I", "'ll", "get", "like", "a", "day", "here", "and", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "That's it, right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "it", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", ":"], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Is there anything else you're up to, other than all this?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anything", "else", "you", "'re", "up", "to", ",", "other", "than", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "There --", "answer_tokens": ["There", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Or is that enough this year, is it?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "that", "enough", "this", "year", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Of all the famous people you've met, who's been the most inspiring to you when you actually met them?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "the", "famous", "people", "you", "'ve", "met", ",", "who", "'s", "been", "the", "most", "inspiring", "to", "you", "when", "you", "actually", "met", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "Oooh.", "answer_tokens": ["Oooh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "Did you meet the president?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "meet", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 675, "question": "What did he say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "\"Hi, I'm Barack.\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Hi", ",", "I", "'m", "Barack", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "Did he know you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "know", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "I think his daughters did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "his", "daughters", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "``", "UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ".", "''", "''"], "qSentId": 692, "question": "He didn't say he watched it religiously?", "question_tokens": ["He", "did", "n't", "say", "he", "watched", "it", "religiously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 693, "answer": "No, no, he wasn't like, \"Oh, I loved you in 'Single Ladies.'\"", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "he", "was", "n't", "like", ",", "``", "Oh", ",", "I", "loved", "you", "in", "'Single", "Ladies", ".", "'", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "Yes, what was she like with you?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "what", "was", "she", "like", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "Great, great.", "answer_tokens": ["Great", ",", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "So, your mother isn't getting demanding about fame, now, right?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "your", "mother", "is", "n't", "getting", "demanding", "about", "fame", ",", "now", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "A little bit, a little bit, a little bit, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "bit", ",", "a", "little", "bit", ",", "a", "little", "bit", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 745, "question": "I mean, that's a bummer, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "bummer", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 746, "answer": "For some people it could be.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "some", "people", "it", "could", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "I mean, are you proud to be Michelle Obama's older brother?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "are", "you", "proud", "to", "be", "Michelle", "Obama", "'s", "older", "brother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 772, "question": "Are you amazed at how she's dealt with becoming first lady?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "amazed", "at", "how", "she", "'s", "dealt", "with", "becoming", "first", "lady", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 773, "answer": "Wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 777, "question": "Who grows up on the south side of Chicago and, as you pointed out, very modest background, and ends up being the first lady?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "grows", "up", "on", "the", "south", "side", "of", "Chicago", "and", ",", "as", "you", "pointed", "out", ",", "very", "modest", "background", ",", "and", "ends", "up", "being", "the", "first", "lady", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNS", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 778, "answer": "Well, the answer is nobody.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "answer", "is", "nobody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Mr. President"]}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 785, "question": "What do you call the president now, when you see him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "call", "the", "president", "now", ",", "when", "you", "see", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 786, "answer": "Oh, when I see him I call him Barack or President Obama or Mr. President.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "when", "I", "see", "him", "I", "call", "him", "Barack", "or", "President", "Obama", "or", "Mr.", "President", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 790, "question": "Doesn't it feel even stranger calling him Mr. President?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "it", "feel", "even", "stranger", "calling", "him", "Mr.", "President", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "VBG", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "It does.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Harvard"]}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", ",", "IN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 795, "question": "Had you heard of him before?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "you", "heard", "of", "him", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 796, "answer": "You know, I had heard she was dating a guy who was a Harvard guy and they worked together in the summer and this, that, and the other.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "had", "heard", "she", "was", "dating", "a", "guy", "who", "was", "a", "Harvard", "guy", "and", "they", "worked", "together", "in", "the", "summer", "and", "this", ",", "that", ",", "and", "the", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 810, "question": "Is it as simple as those things that he was doing means he's a good man?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "as", "simple", "as", "those", "things", "that", "he", "was", "doing", "means", "he", "'s", "a", "good", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 811, "answer": "You know, it's hard when you get fatigued to shield your real personality.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "hard", "when", "you", "get", "fatigued", "to", "shield", "your", "real", "personality", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 826, "question": "When was the moment -- when Michelle was dating Barack, when was the moment that you realized this guy may be something special politically?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "moment", "--", "when", "Michelle", "was", "dating", "Barack", ",", "when", "was", "the", "moment", "that", "you", "realized", "this", "guy", "may", "be", "something", "special", "politically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 827, "answer": "Oh, I had no idea at the time when I met him.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "had", "no", "idea", "at", "the", "time", "when", "I", "met", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michelle", "Barack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 838, "question": "What's the moment like for you personally, on a human level, when you walk into the White House for the first time with your brother-in-law as the president of the United States?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "moment", "like", "for", "you", "personally", ",", "on", "a", "human", "level", ",", "when", "you", "walk", "into", "the", "White", "House", "for", "the", "first", "time", "with", "your", "brother-in-law", "as", "the", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 839, "answer": "Well, I got to tell you, the first thing, Piers, that struck me was how small the inside of the White House was.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "got", "to", "tell", "you", ",", "the", "first", "thing", ",", "Piers", ",", "that", "struck", "me", "was", "how", "small", "the", "inside", "of", "the", "White", "House", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House", "United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 840, "question": "It's a lot smaller than you think, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "lot", "smaller", "than", "you", "think", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 841, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 851, "question": "But was it a surreal moment for you?", "question_tokens": ["But", "was", "it", "a", "surreal", "moment", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 852, "answer": "And it still is.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "it", "still", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 859, "question": "Something that annoys you most when you see them described as whatever?", "question_tokens": ["Something", "that", "annoys", "you", "most", "when", "you", "see", "them", "described", "as", "whatever", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "JJS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 860, "answer": "You know, I would love to tell you that there was something that bothers me, but nothing that anybody says bothers me.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "would", "love", "to", "tell", "you", "that", "there", "was", "something", "that", "bothers", "me", ",", "but", "nothing", "that", "anybody", "says", "bothers", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 867, "question": "You never did?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 868, "answer": "No, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 875, "question": "How did you feel when you discovered that your brother- in-law had ordered the mission, the successful mission that killed Osama bin Laden?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "discovered", "that", "your", "brother-", "in-law", "had", "ordered", "the", "mission", ",", "the", "successful", "mission", "that", "killed", "Osama", "bin", "Laden", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 876, "answer": "Well, I have to say I was probably like most of the people who heard the news.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "to", "say", "I", "was", "probably", "like", "most", "of", "the", "people", "who", "heard", "the", "news", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Osama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 884, "question": "And, finally, will you be out on the stump for him next election campaign?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "finally", ",", "will", "you", "be", "out", "on", "the", "stump", "for", "him", "next", "election", "campaign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 885, "answer": "Well, if they need me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "they", "need", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 919, "question": "You're threatening me with physical violence, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "threatening", "me", "with", "physical", "violence", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 920, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]